by RentAnAdviser.com
I found a love for me
Darling just dive right in
And follow my lead
Well I found a girl beautiful
and sweet
I never knew you were the
someone waiting for me
'Cause we were just kids
when we fell in love
Not knowing what it was
I will not give you up this time
But darling, just kiss me slow,
your heart is all I own
And in your eyes you're holding mine
Baby, I'm dancing in the dark
with you between my arms
****foot on the grass, listening
to our favorite song
When you said you looked a mess, I
whispered underneath my breath
But you heard it, darling,
you look perfect tonight
Well I found a woman, stronger
than anyone I know
She shares my dreams, I hope that
someday I'll share her home
I found a love, to carry more
than just my secrets
To carry love, to carry
children of our own
We are still kids, but
we're so in love
Fighting against all odds
I know we'll be alright this time
Darling, just hold my hand
Be my girl, I'll be your man
I see my future in your eyes
Baby, I'm dancing in the dark,
with you between my arms
****foot on the grass, listening
to our favorite song
When I saw you in that dress,
looking so beautiful
I don't deserve this, darling,
you look perfect tonight
Baby, I'm dancing in the dark,
with you between my arms
****foot on the grass, listening
to our favorite song
I have faith in what I see
Now I know I have met
an angel in person
And she looks perfect
I don't deserve this
You look perfect tonight
by RentAnAdviser.com